# Shiyou(Alan) Huang 419D HRBB, Texas A&M University College Station, TX, USA 77840

Curriculum Vitae

#### Research Interests

My areas of interest are model checking, system security, and bug reproduction. The goal of my research is to help develop automated systems combining program analysis, hardware advances, and systematic testing to improve the reliability and security of the software.

#### Education

9/2015–present **Ph.D. Candidate in Computer Science**, *Texas A&M University*, USA.

Advisor: Jeff Huang

9/2011–6/2015 B.E. in Computer Science, Huazhong University of Science and Technology

(HUST), Wuhan, China.

GPA: 4.0/4.0

#### **Publication**

USENIX ATC Shiyou Huang, Towards Production-Run Heisenbugs Reproduction on Commer-

2017 *cial Hardware*, Proceedings of USENIX Annual Technical Conference (USENIX ATC), July 2017.

ECOOP 2017 **Shiyou Huang**, Speeding Up Maximal Causality Reduction with Static Dependency Analysis, 31st European Conference on Object-Oriented Programming, 2017.

OOPSLA 2016 **Shiyou Huang**, *Maximal Causality Reduction for TSO and PSO*, Proceedings of ACM SIGPLAN conference on Object-Oriented Programming, Systems, Languages, and Applications, 2016.

ICSE SRC 2016 **Shiyou Huang**, Maximally stateless model checking for concurrent bugs under relaxed memory models, Proceedings of the 38th International Conference on Software Engineering Companion, 2016.

#### Honor & Awards

June 2017 Student Scholar for  $50^{th}$  Turing Award Celebration.

Spring 2017 Graduate Research Excellence Award, Department of CSE, Texas A&M.

OOPSLA 2016 SIGPLAN PAC Award, OOPSLA, 2016.

ICSE 2016 ACM's SRC Travel Award, ICSE, 2016.

ICSE 2016 SIGSOFT CAPS Award, ICSE, 2016.

ICSE 2016 Third Place, Student Research Competition, ICSE'16.

2012,2014 Excellent Academic Performance Scholarship, HUST.

## Service

Sub-reviewer PLDI'17, PPoPP'17, FSE'16.

AE Committee PPoPP'17.

### Research Experience

9/2015 - 9/2016 Graduate Research Assistant, ASER GROUP, PARASOL LAB, Texas A&M

University.

Advisor: Jeff Huang

5/2014 – 8/2014 Research Intern, SCTSL LAB, Huazhong University of Science and Technology,

Wuhan, China.

Advisor: Zhi Zhou and Fangming Liu.

## Teaching Experience

Spring 2018 CSCE314: Programming Languages, Haskell & Java, Texas A&M University.

Teaching Assistant

Spring 2017 **CSCE431: Software Engineering**, Texas A&M University.

Teaching Assistant

Fall 2016 **CSCE606: Software Engineering**, Texas A&M University.

Teaching Assistant

#### Skills

Languages Java, C/C++, Python, Ruby.

Tools ASM, Z3, LLVM.